I would also like to shout out the people in our lives who we send particular content to, okay?
I want to shout out my boy Brennan, who I only send videos of whales to.
I want to shout out my boy Luke, who I send all videos of interesting wildlife,
as well as anything referencing Lord of the Rings and wizardry.
I want to shout out my friend Natasha, who we send anything that represents friendships that exist in the world that we want to exist in.
Cool friends, that's us.
I want to shout out Marvin, who I send all things Jamaican to.
Why? Because Marvin is a yaddy them.
I want to shout out Ori.
We have been sending each other future toxic texts and memes since like 2019.
I want to shout out my boy, who we send all things OD New York, all things OD, and all things OD Cancer.
Girl, you from the city. You not demure. You dead ass.
I want to shout out Willard Hill, who I'm sending anything that is just complete nonsense funny to.
Because you know what? He's gonna get it.
I've been sent from Africa to destroy you.
To destroy me?
Yes.
Yeah?
Rambo, Rambo, Rambo, Rambo, Rambo, Rambo, Rambo, Rambo.
What's your name?
Go away!
Don't do me that shit.
What's your name?
Rambo, Rambo, Rambo.
Why would you put this on me?
Rambo, Rambo.
Why would you do this?
Joke.
I want to shout out James Bland, who I'm going to send anything OD gay to.
What does LGBTQ plus mean? Is it like the premium gay?
Melissa is always going to keep me up to date on all things gymnastics, especially Israel getting banned from the world championships.
My Patreon gets the cat content.
If it's cats, my cats especially, the SEAL squad is getting it.
So tag the people in the comments who you be sending specific things to and what you send them.